PIYUSH

Dumraon · 9610141624 piyushraj1129@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/piyush-2818/



Experienced Campus Ambassador with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in SEO Copywriting, HTML, JavaScript, Video Editing, and Soft Skills. Strong entrepreneurship professional with a Bachelor of Technology majoring in Computer Science and engineering from Lovely Professional University.

EXPERIENCE

JAN 2022 - TILL DATE

FOUNDER, PAPPU PROGRAMMER

A community for programmers by programmers to help learn skills and coding languages in the best possible way.

JULY 2020 – TILL DATE

CHIEF COMMUNICATION OFFICER, MAGNESIA

Got appointed as CCO in one of the student organizations in LPU to manage cultural and technical events.

MARCH 2021 – TILL DATE

FOUNDER, INSANE PIYUSH [YOUTUBE CHANNEL]

A YouTube channel for college students to guide them on how to make their college life better, learn skills and make money while they learn.

DEC 2021 - MARCH 2022

SOCIAL MEDIA HEAD, CODING NINJAS LPU

Managed the social media team of coding ninja's LPU chapter and helped it grow and conduct events in online mode.

MAY 2021 - JULY 2021

VOLUNTEER, TURNING POINT CONSULTANCY SERVICES

I made posters and videos on COVID- 19 awareness. I also raised funds for food donations among poor people in different cities during the COVID-19 outbreak.

JULY 2020 - JUNE 2021

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR, BRICS CCI YOUNG LEADER

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

TECHNICAL LEAD, RHINO GEEK

EDUCATION

JULY 2020- TILL DATE

B. TECH, LOVELY PROFESSIONAL UNIVERSITY

Pursuing my bachelor's in technology majoring in Computer Science and Engineering with an academic CGPA of 7.4.

2018-2020

INTERMEDIATE, R.N.SAH SARVODAY COLLEGE ROHTAS

Passed my senior secondary major in PCM (Physics, Chemistry, and Mathematics) with a percentage of 84.

SKILLS

- C++
- Python
- Video editing
- Graphic designing

- JavaScript
- HTML and CSS
- React Js
- Bootstrap and jQuery

PROJECTS

- AI chatbot in smart India hackathon 2022
- Portfolio using HTML, CSS, and JS
- Animation website using JavaScript
- Real estate website using HTML, CSS, JS
- Inventory management system using python and MySQL.

ACTIVITIES

- Organized Vanquish mega event
- Hosted a gay activist of the united nation on the behalf of LPU.
- Organized event of Suhani shah the mentalist.
- Winner of the vlog event.
- Runner up of reel-o-insta event.